[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "4, 8, 16, ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "4, 8, 16, 32",
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "2 + 2 x 2 = ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "6, 8, 16, 32",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "▢ + ▢ = 8\n❍ + ▢ = 14\n△ + ◯ = 11\n△ = ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "6, 8, 16, 32",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "6 = 30\n3 = 15\n7 = 35\n2 = ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "6, 10, 16, 32",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "4, 11, 18, ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "6, 10, 16, 25",
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "5 + 5 x 5 - 5 = ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "6, 10, 16, 25",
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "A + B = 60\nA - B = 40\nA / B = ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "5, 10, 16, 25",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "A + B = 60\nA - B = 40\nA / B = ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "5, 10, 16, 25",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "13, 18 = 31\n7, 25 = 32\n12, 30 = 42\n26, 13 = ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "5, 10, 16, 39",
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "type": 1,
    "question": "8 - 8 / 4 x 3 = ?",
    "style": {
      "shape": "rectangle",
      "color": "blue"
    },
    "options": "2, 10, 16, 25",
    "answer": "2"
  }
]